I
You
You ungrateful brat
Just like they say, a married daughter
is like spilled water
You're always siding with outsiders
How am I ungrateful
Daniel dumped you at my house
Did Lewes or I say anything
You said you'd help out
But how much did you actually do
Lewes and his parents did everything
Look at her
She's complaining we didn't do enough
The old saying is right
After three days
at a daughter's place
you've overstayed your welcome
Thank God we still have a son
You
How could you say that
It's true that lately
you've been working hard
The help arrives tomorrow
You won't have to do anything then
I have a son
I won't stay with an outsider like you
If it weren't for the secr
Anyway, not for another day
will I stay here
Fine
Since you want to find
your own son
I won't stop you
But Daniel
can barely take care of himself right now
Don't regret it when you go back
That's none of your business
Daniel is about to
make a huge comeback
The two of us
are going to live off our son's success
You'd better worry about
yourself
Aren't you just
relying on that secret recipe to make money
Soon that money
won't be so easy to make
What did my father mean
What's the fuss about now
Cynthia
Your parents only came here
for my recipe
What